[{"answer": " Hey Lucy.  Do you have some time to talk about next weeks business trip wit", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Sure.  Im free for the next 30 minutes.  Whats on your mind", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hey Lucy.  Do you have some time to talk about next weeks business trip wit", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Well, since this is my first trip with the company I wanted to confirm some detail", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Sure.  Im free for the next 30 minutes.  Whats on your mind", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Sure.  Shoot", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, since this is my first trip with the company I wanted to confirm some detail", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " OK.  So, were leaving on Monday from Hartsfield International Airport an", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Sure.  Shoot", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " No, we dont have to.  The company car will pick us up and take us there.  Tha", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 27, "question": " OK.  So, were leaving on Monday from Hartsfield International Airport an", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Oh, thats good.  What time will they pick us up", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 30, "question": " No, we dont have to.  The company car will pick us up and take us there.  Tha", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Our flight departs at 11am, so they should pick us up between 8 and 9 am", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Oh, thats good.  What time will they pick us up", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " All right.  How much do you usually pack for these trips", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Our flight departs at 11am, so they should pick us up between 8 and 9 am", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I usually take one small suitcase and a suit bag.  Well need suits for each da", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 36, "question": " All right.  How much do you usually pack for these trips", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Do we get to go out to dinner and do things in the evening", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 40, "question": " I usually take one small suitcase and a suit bag.  Well need suits for each da", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Sure.  After the meetings end in the day were free to do whatever we want in th", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Do we get to go out to dinner and do things in the evening", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Thats cool.  So I guess Ill need to bring enough money to cover dinner eac", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Sure.  After the meetings end in the day were free to do whatever we want in th", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " No, the company pays for our expenses on the trip, including food", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Thats cool.  So I guess Ill need to bring enough money to cover dinner eac", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 50, "question": " No, the company pays for our expenses on the trip, including food", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": "  Yeah.  We get a per diem each day to cover food and transportation", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " How much do we get", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 52, "question": "  Yeah.  We get a per diem each day to cover food and transportation", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " It depends on the city were traveling to.  Since were going to New York thi", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 53, "question": " How much do we get", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " How do we get the per diem", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 57, "question": " It depends on the city were traveling to.  Since were going to New York thi", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": "We have to use our own money to pay for things on the trip.  Then, when we ge", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 58, "question": " How do we get the per diem", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " So anything we buy we get reimbursed for", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 61, "question": "We have to use our own money to pay for things on the trip.  Then, when we ge", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Not everything.  Just food and transportation.  You have to save your receipts fo", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 62, "question": " So anything we buy we get reimbursed for", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  Thanks for telling me that.  I wouldnt have thought to save all th", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Not everything.  Just food and transportation.  You have to save your receipts fo", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Yeah, dont lose them.  I did once and they wouldnt pay me back for m", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Oh, OK.  Thanks for telling me that.  I wouldnt have thought to save all th", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Thats terrible", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Yeah, dont lose them.  I did once and they wouldnt pay me back for m", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I know.  It cost me a lot of money", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Thats terrible", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I wanted to ask you one more thing too.  If we finish early, like on Thursday, d", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I know.  It cost me a lot of money", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Well, we never really finish early because we have meetings scheduled on Frida", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 84, "question": " I wanted to ask you one more thing too.  If we finish early, like on Thursday, d", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " OK.  I was just wondering", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Well, we never really finish early because we have meetings scheduled on Frida", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " I think youll enjoy the business trip.  Its nice to get out of the office once in ", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 91, "question": " OK.  I was just wondering", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Yeah, Im kind of looking forward to it.  Thanks for clearing all that up for me", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 95, "question": " I think youll enjoy the business trip.  Its nice to get out of the office once in ", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Any time", "docId": "03-03", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Yeah, Im kind of looking forward to it.  Thanks for clearing all that up for me", "qSentId": 95}]
